Guide to the Francis B. (Francis Butler) Loomis Papers: microfilm, 1897-1939
Department of Special Collections
- Descendants of Joseph Loomis in America and His Antecedents in the Old World, Series 8; 1 microfilm reel
National Association of Manufacturers Roll I Folder 5 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 11, Folder 15,
National Bank of Santo Domingo Roll II Folder 11
National Republican Committee Roll I Folder 6
Naumburg, A. Roll I Folder 5 Roll II Folder 11
The Negro Trail Blazers of California See Delilah Beasley Roll I Folder 1
Neville, Edwin L. Roll II Folder 16
Nevins, Allan Roll II Folder 10
Newcomb, William A. Roll II Folder 11
Newhall, W. Mays Roll II Folder 17
Newlands, Francis G. Roll I Folder 4
New York and Bermudez Asphalt Company Roll I Folder 1, Folder 5, Folder 7, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 15, Folder 17
New York Board of Trade and Transportation Roll II Folder 11
New York Central Railroad Roll I Folder 6
The New York Evening Post Roll I Folder 3, Folder 5
The New York Herald Roll I Folder 5 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 11, Folder 13, Folder 16, Folder 17, Folder 18
The New York Journal Roll II Folder 15
New York Life Insurance Company Roll II Folder 11
The New York Sun Roll I Folder 2, Folder 6 Roll II Folder 11, Folder 13, Folder 17
The New York Tribune Roll II Folder 9, Folder 11, Folder 17
The New York World Roll II Folder 14
Nicaraguan Canal Roll I Folder 2
Nicholas II, Czar of Russia Roll II Folder 10
Nicholson, D. Roll II Folder 11, Folder 13
Niles, W. W. Roll II Folder 17
Nimitz, Chester Roll II Folder 16
Nobel Prize for Peace Roll I Folder 3 Roll II Folder 15
North American Review Roll I Folder 1
Norton, Thomas H. Roll II Folder 11
Oakland Tribune Roll I Folder 1, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 7 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 15, Folder 17, Folder 18
O'Connor, Basil Roll I Folder 1
Odell, H. Allen Roll II Folder 11
Ohio Republican State Executive Committee Roll II Folder 11
O'Laughlin, John C. Roll I Folder 8 Roll II Folder 12, Folder 15
Olavarria, J. A. Roll II Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 12, Folder 15
Olcott, R. Morgan Roll I Folder 1, Folder 7 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 12
O'Neal, W. C. Roll I Folder 6
Orbeck, Andrew J. Roll II Folder 12
Order of the Crown of Italy Roll II Folder 9
Oregon Historical Quarterly Roll I Folder 8
Orinoco Corporation Roll I Folder 5
The Orinoco Shipping and Trading Company Ltd. Roll II Folder 12, Folder 15
The Orinoco Steamship Company Roll I Folder 4, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 12
Orinoco Trading and Transportation Company Roll I Folder 8
Ormsbee, Talcott Roll I Folder 8
Osborne, John B. Roll II Folder 12
Ospina Perez, M. Roll I Folder 6
Oura, Kanetake Roll II Folder 15
Outlook Magazine Roll I Folder 4 Roll II Folder 15
Overstreet, Jesse Roll II Folder 12
Pacific League of International Relations Roll II Folder 9
Pacific Mail Steamship Company Roll II Folder 15
Paez, Federico Roll II Folder 18
Page, Thomas Nelson Roll II Folder 11
Paish, George Roll I Folder 3
Palmer, Frederick Roll I Folder 6
Panama Canal Roll I Folder 2, Folder 4, Folder 7 Roll II Folder 12, Folder 18
Panama Crisis Roll I Folder 1, Folder 2, Folder 4, Folder 6 Roll II Folder 10, Folder 12, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 17, Folder 18
Panama Pacific Exposition Roll I Folder 8
Panama, Republic of Roll I Folder 2
Pan American Bulletin Roll II Folder 15
Pan American Conference Roll I Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 8
Pan American Railroad Roll I Folder 4
Pan American Union Roll I Folder 1, Folder 5 Roll II Folder 18
Pan Pacific Society Roll I Folder 3
Paquet, Norbert A. Roll II Folder 17
Paredes, Antonio Roll II Folder 12
The Paris Daily Herald Roll I Folder 7 Roll II Folder 16
Parish, W. H. Roll I Folder 5
Parker, Frank Roll I Folder 5 Roll II Folder 12, Folder 14, Folder 15
Parmelee, James Roll I Folder 8 Roll II Folder 12
Parparen, Ramon Roll I Folder 5
Parsons, J. R. Roll II Folder 14
Patchin, Robert H. Roll II Folder 11
Patterson, Lila Roll II Folder 10
Patterson, Raymond Roll II Folder 12
Paul, J. de J. Roll I Folder 5
Pauncefote, Julian Roll II Folder 17
Pearson's Magazine Roll II Folder 17
Pecci, Ludovico Roll I Folder 4
Peixotto, G. D. M. Roll II Folder 16
Pelps, William H. Roll I Folder 5
Penfield, William L. Roll I Folder 4, Folder 5 Roll II Folder 12, Folder 17
Penrose, Boies Roll II Folder 12
The People's Government Roll I Folder 8
Pepper, Charles M. Roll II Folder 12
Perdicaris, Ion Roll I Folder 4
Perkins, Dexter See The Monroe Doctrine Roll I Folder 1
Perkins, George C. Roll II Folder 12, Folder 13
Permanent Court of International Justice Roll I Folder 8
Pershing, John J. Roll I Folder 4
Pershing, Mary Roll I Folder 4
Ptain, Philippe Roll I Folder 2
Petroleum Concessions Ltd. Roll II Folder 17
Petroleum Times Roll I Folder 4
Phelan, James D. Roll II Folder 12
Phelps, William E. Roll I Folder 5
Philadelphia Evening Telegraph Roll II Folder 13
Philbin, Eugene A. Roll II Folder 13
Philippine Question Roll I Folder 1, Folder 3, Folder 6 Roll II Folder 18
Phillips, H. C. Roll II Folder 9
Phillips, John R. Roll II Folder 12, Folder 13
Phillips, Roland Roll II Folder 12
Pickleman, Sebastian Roll II Folder 9
Pierce, Herbert H. D. Roll II Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 14
Pike, William J. Roll II Folder 12
Pilgrim's Society Roll II Folder 10
Pillsbury, E. S. Roll II Folder 12
Pinelli, Philippe Roll II Folder 17
Pittman, Gerry Roll I Folder 6 Roll II Folder 12
Pius X, Pope Roll I Folder 4
Platt, Orville H. Roll I Folder 6 Roll II Folder 11, Folder 13, Folder 14
Plumacher, E. H. Roll I Folder 3, Folder 5
Plumley, Frank Roll I Folder 2
Polk, Willis K. Roll II Folder 10
Porter, Clarence Roll I Folder 4 Roll II Folder 13
Porter, Horace Roll I Folder 8 Roll II Folder 12, Folder 13
Post (Oakland?) Roll I Folder 1
Powell, W. F. Roll I Folder 4 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 13
Powers, Horace H. Roll I Folder 4
Press Release Roll II Folder 11
Prince, John D. Roll II Folder 11, Folder 17
Prostkauer, Saul Roll II Folder 13
Puck Roll II Folder 13
Purbrey, Eugene Roll II Folder 13
Quay, Matthew S. Roll II Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 18
Quill Club, New York Roll II Folder 9, Folder 11, Folder 15
Radcliffe, [J. R. S.?] Roll II Folder 10
Raisuli, Mohamed Roll II Folder 9, Folder 18
Ralston, Jackson H. Roll I Folder 5
Rampol, Cardinal Roll I Folder 4
Reciprocity Treaty, Cuba, United States Roll II Folder 17
Redding, Joseph D. Roll I Folder 4
Reid, J. Whitelaw Roll I Folder 3, Folder 4 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 11, Folder 13
Rendon, [?] Roll I Folder 4
Reyes, Rafael Roll I Folder 2, Folder 7 Roll II Folder 11
Reynolds, J. B. Roll II Folder 13, Folder 14
Rocco, [?] Roll I Folder 2
Rockefeller, John D. Jr. Roll II Folder 13, Folder 16
Rodgers, I. S. Roll II Folder 13
Rodriquez, Dimetrio Roll I Folder 5 Roll II Folder 16
Roehl, Eduardo Roll I Folder 5
Rogers, Edith N. Roll II Folder 13
Rogers, John J. Roll II Folder 16
Roosevelt, Alice Roll I Folder 4
Roosevelt, Franklin Roll II Folder 12
Roosevelt, Theodore Roll I Folder 1, Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 6 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 17, Folder 18
Root, Elihu Roll I Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 6, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 10, Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 17, Folder 18
Rosen, Baron Roll II Folder 12, Folder 14
Ross, Charles B. Roll I Folder 4 Roll II Folder 12
Rostand, [?] Roll II Folder 10, Folder 13
Rourke, Thomas Roll I Folder 5
Rouvier, Maurice Roll I Folder 2 Roll II Folder 10, Folder 13
Rowell, Chester Roll I Folder 1, Folder 4 Roll II Folder 15
Royal Dutch Company Roll II Folder 16
Royce, L. W. Roll II Folder 12
Russell, Lindsay Roll I Folder 3
Russell, William W. Roll I Folder 1, Folder 3, Folder 5, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 12, Folder 15, Folder 16, Folder 17
Russo-Japanese War Roll I Folder 1, Folder 2 Roll II Folder 14
Ruyssenairs, L. H. Roll I Folder 1
St. Andrews University Roll I Folder 3
St. John, C. M. Roll II Folder 15
St. Louis Exposition Roll I Folder 8
St. Mary's Roll I Folder 4
Sakai, Tadusaki Roll II Folder 12, Folder 15, Folder 17
Salinas bonds Roll I Folder 3
Sammons, Thomas Roll II Folder 16
Sampson, Archibald J. Roll II Folder 15
Sampson, William T. Roll I Folder 4 Roll II Folder 15
Sanabria, Gustavo Roll I Folder 5
San Antonio Daily Express Roll II Folder 9
Sanborn, Edward H. Roll I Folder 5 Roll II Folder 15
Sanchez, Juan Roll I Folder 4 Roll II Folder 13
Sanderson, T. A. Roll II Folder 15
San Domingo Finance Company of New York Roll II Folder 11
San Domingo Improvement Company of New York Roll I Folder 7 Roll II Folder 11
San Francisco Bulletin Roll I Folder 1 Roll II Folder 12, Folder 13
San Francisco Examiner Roll I Folder 2, Folder 4, Folder 6 Roll II Folder 18
San Francisco Exposition Roll I Folder 3
San Francisco News Roll I Folder 5
San Joaquin Valley, California Roll I Folder 1
Santiago, Department of Roll I Folder 7
Sargent, Nathan Roll II Folder 12, Folder 15
Satolli, Cardinal Roll I Folder 4
Saturday Evening Post Roll I Folder 1, Folder 7 Roll II Folder 18
Saturday Review of Literature Roll II Folder 16
Schley, Winfield Roll I Folder 8
Schwan, Theodore Roll I Folder 8
Schwarzenstein, Mumm von Roll II Folder 12
Scony Oil Roll I Folder 5
Scott, Henry L. Roll I Folder 4, Folder 7, Folder 8
Scripps-McRae Association Roll I Folder 4
Search, Theodore C. Roll I Folder 5 Roll II Folder 15
Seeger, Eugene Roll II Folder 15
Seidmore, George F. Roll I Folder 6
Seijas, Ramon Roll I Folder 3
Seligman Brothers of London Roll II Folder 15
Shafter, William R. Roll I Folder 7, Folder 8
Sharp, Amor W. Roll II Folder 15
Shaw, Albert Roll I Folder 1 Roll II Folder 14, Folder 15
Shaw, Howland Roll II Folder 16
Shell Oil Company Roll II Folder 10
Sherman, John Roll I Folder 6 Roll II Folder 11, Folder 13, Folder 15
Sherrill, Charles Roll I Folder 4
Shortridge, Samuel M. Roll II Folder 15
Sigsbee, Charles D. Roll I Folder 4 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 14, Folder 16
Simmons, Roger A. Roll II Folder 15
Sinclair Concession Roll I Folder 4
Skiff, Frederick J. Roll I Folder 3 Roll II Folder 12, Folder 14
Skinner, Helen W. Roll I Folder 4
Skinner, Robert P. Roll I Folder 2, Folder 4 Roll II Folder 16
Small, Sam Roll II Folder 17
Smiley, Albert K. Roll II Folder 9
Smith, Al Roll I Folder 4
Smith, Charles E. Roll I Folder 5, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 12, Folder 17, Folder 18
Smith, Warren Roll I Folder 4
Smyth, William D. Roll II Folder 17
Snyder, G. Roll II Folder 17
Southern Pacific Company Roll I Folder 4
South Manchuria Railway Company Roll I Folder 6
Spanish-American War Roll I Folder 1, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 9
Spectator Roll II Folder 10
Speransky, Julia G. Roll II Folder 17
Speyer, James Roll II Folder 17
Springfield News Roll I Folder 6
Stabler, Herbert J. Roll I Folder 5
Stamp, Josiah Roll II Folder 10
Standard Oil Bulletin Roll II Folder 10
Standard Oil Company Roll I Folder 1 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 16, Folder 17, Folder 18
Standard Oil Company of California Roll I Folder 1, Folder 8
Standard Oil of New Jersey Roll I Folder 5
Stanford, Mrs. Leland Roll II Folder 17
Stanford University Roll II Folder 17
Stanton, Philip Roll II Folder 9
Stearns, Frank W. Roll II Folder 16
Steinhart, [?] Roll II Folder 17, Folder 18
Stephens, Virginia Roll I Folder 1
Stevenson, Adlai E. Roll II Folder 9
Stimson, Henry L. Roll II Folder 15, Folder 16, Folder 17
Sthamer, Frederick Roll II Folder 16
Stoddard, Henry L. Roll II Folder 17
Stokes, W. E. D. Roll II Folder 17
Stratton, F. S. Roll II Folder 17
Straus, Oscar S. Roll II Folder 17
Surez, Eduardo Roll I Folder 1
Sullivan, Mark Roll II Folder 9, Folder 15
Sutro, Adolph Roll I Folder 4
Sutro, Oscar Roll I Folder 2, Folder 8
Swann, Albert W. Roll II Folder 17
Swanson, Charles E. Roll I Folder 6
Swayne, Charles Roll I Folder 6
Taft, Robert A. Roll II Folder 17
Taft, William H. Roll I Folder 1, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 6, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 16, Folder 17, Folder 18
Takahira, Kogoro Roll II Folder 12, Folder 17
Taylor, H. C. Roll II Folder 17
Tejera, Emiliano Roll I Folder 4 Roll II Folder 9
Tello, Aristides Roll I Folder 5 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 10
Tennessee Copper Company Roll I Folder 2
Thayer, W. Roscoe Roll I Folder 1 Roll II Folder 10, Folder 11, Folder 17
Theodore Roosevelt and His Time See J. B. Bishop Roll I Folder 1
Theodore Roosevelt and the Kaiser in 1905 See Bunau-Varilla Roll I Folder 2
Thompson, John Roll I Folder 8 Roll II Folder 15, Folder 18
Tisza, Istvan Roll II Folder 12
Tobin Memorandum Roll II Folder 11
Tokyo, International Exposition of Roll I Folder 7 Roll II Folder 15
Toledo Trujillo, [?] Roll I Folder 5
Torres, Mohammad Ben Larbi Roll II Folder 9, Folder 18
Torres Cardenas, [?] Roll I Folder 5
Tower, Charlemagne Roll II Folder 14, Folder 18
Townsend, George A. Roll II Folder 18
Townsend, Lawrence Roll II Folder 9
Truman, Harry Roll I Folder 4 Roll II Folder 16
Turin, International Exposition of Roll I Folder 3, Folder 4 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 11
Tyler, George S. Roll II Folder 10, Folder 13
Underwood, Oscar W. Roll I Folder 8
Underwood, Rufus A. Roll II Folder 18
Union Pacific Railroad Roll II Folder 18
United Press Roll II Folder 18
United States Consul, Turin Roll I Folder 4
United States Legation, Bogota Roll I Folder 1
United States Legation, Lisbon Roll I Folder 1
United States Legation, Spain Roll I Folder 3
United States Steel Corporation Roll I Folder 3 Roll II Folder 18
Upham, Fred Roll I Folder 4
Valencia Railroad Roll II Folder 9
Vandenberg, Arthur Roll II Folder 16
van Loon, Hendrik Willem Roll II Folder 10
Vsquez, Leon Roll II Folder 9, Folder 13
Vatin, Periguon Roll I Folder 2
Vavasour-Noel, John Roll II Folder 18
Velsquez, [?] Roll I Folder 4 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 16
Velaz, Coiticaa Roll I Folder 5
The Venezuelan Herald Roll I Folder 8 Roll II Folder 9
Verdunisation Roll I Folder 2
Vicentini, Cesar Roll I Folder 3 Roll II Folder 12 Folder 15
Vidal, M. Roll II Folder 12
Vignauer, Henry Roll II Folder 18
Villiers, [?] Roll II Folder 10
Villimil, Jose Roll I Folder 4
von Lutz, Baron Roll II Folder 12
von Sternberg, H. S. Roll II Folder 14 Folder 17
Wada, Hikojiro Roll II Folder 15 Folder 17 Folder 18
Wadsworth, James W. Jr. Roll II Folder 17 Folder 18
Walker, William Roll II Folder 10 Folder 13
Wallace, Mrs. Hugh Roll I Folder 4
Warren, Charles B. Roll I Folder 7 Roll II Folder 18
Washington Herald Roll II Folder 10 Folder 12
Washington Post Roll II Folder 11
Watterson, Henry Roll I Folder 3 Roll II Folder 10
Weeks, John W. Roll II Folder 9 Folder 18
Weid, Smith M. Roll II Folder 11
Welles, Sumner Roll II Folder 18
Westendorp and Company Roll II Folder 11
Westinghouse Company Roll II Folder 9
Wheeler, Benjamin Roll II Folder 18
Wheeler, Ernest Roll II Folder 10
Wheeler, Joseph Roll I Folder 8 Roll II Folder 14
Wheeler, William R. Roll II Folder 12
White, Albert B. Roll II Folder 18
White, Andrew D. Roll II Folder 10
White, Harry Roll I Folder 7
White, Henry Roll I Folder 6 Roll II Folder 10 Folder 12 Folder 18
Whitney, Harry Roll II Folder 15
Wiart, Carton de Roll II Folder 18
Wiborg, Frank B. Roll II Folder 9 Folder 10
Wickersham, George W. Roll II Folder 18
Wilbur, Ray Lyman Roll II Folder 18
Wilder, Amos P. Roll II Folder 18
Wilkie, Wendell Roll II Folder 16
William II, King of Germany Roll I Folder 2
Williams, Oscar F. Roll II Folder 14
Willis, Frank B. Roll I Folder 2 Folder 8
Willys, John Roll II Folder 16
Wilson, Henry P. Roll I Folder 5 Roll II Folder 18
Wilson, Hugh Roll II Folder 16
Wilson, Huntington Roll II Folder 18
Wilson, Woodrow Roll I Folder 1, Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 6, Folder 8 Roll II Folder 10, Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 15, Folder 17
Wise, Henry A. Roll II Folder 18
Witte, Sergey Y. Roll I Folder 2
Wood, Leonard Roll I Folder 8 Roll II Folder 17, Folder 18
Woodard, J. H. Roll II Folder 18
Woodford, Stewart Roll II Folder 18
Woodworth, B. Roll II Folder 15
Wozan, Shereef of See Mulay Ali Roll II Folder 9
Wright, Robert K. Roll I Folder 1, Folder 5 Roll II Folder 9, Folder 16, Folder 18
Wurlitzer, Howard Roll I Folder 5 Roll II Folder 18
Wyandot Union Republican Roll I Folder 4
Yale Review Roll II Folder 10
Yale University Roll II Folder 13
Ybarra, Alejandro Roll I Folder 1, Folder 5
Yeiser, H. C. Roll I Folder 5 Roll II Folder 18
Y.M.C.A. Roll II Folder 9
Young, Ella Roll II Folder 18
Young, Owen D. Roll II Folder 15
Zimmerman, [?] Roll II Folder 14, Folder 18
Zuloaga, Nicomedes Jr. Roll I Folder 5
Zumeta, Caesar Roll II Folder 18
Index II
Adams, Philip Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Adams, Robert Roll III Book 2
Adams, W. N. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Addison, A. D. Roll IV Book 4
Adee, Alvey Roll V Folder 20
The Advertiser Roll V Folder 22
Akers, E. A. Roll III Book 1
Alden, C. E. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Alderman, A. D. Roll IV Book 3, Book 4, Book 5
Alderman, Edwin A. Roll III Book 2
Aldrich, Nelson W. Roll IV Book 3 Roll V Folder 23
Alger, Russell A. Roll IV Book 3
Alien Land Law Roll V Folder 23
Alkire, A. N. Roll III Book 2
Allen, Andrew H. Roll III Book 2
Allen, Horace N. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Allen, W. Roll IV Book 4
Allison, William B. Roll III Book 2
Almond, Harry J. Roll V Folder 19
American Historical Society Roll V Folder 24
American Red Cross Roll V Folder 24
American Security and Trust Company Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Andara, M. L. J. Roll IV Book 4
Anderson, A. S. Roll III Book 1
Anderson, Edward Roll III Book 2
Anderson, Frank Roll V Folder 24
Anderson, George E. Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Andrade, Ignacio Roll V Folder 19
Andrews, Avery D. Roll IV Book 3
Andrews, Loring Roll IV Book 4
Arbanell, J. R. Roll IV Book 4
Argentine Legation Roll IV Book 3
Argentine Mission Roll III Book 1
The Argonaut Roll V Folder 23
Arkell, W. V. Roll III Book 2
Armour, Ogden Roll III Book 2
Armstrong, George W. Roll IV Book 3
Armstrong, R. B. Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Arnold, H. B. Roll IV Book 4
Arnot, Raymond Roll III Book 2
Arosemena, Carlos C. Roll III Book 2
Associated Press Roll V Folder 22
Athey, D. Charles Roll IV Book 3
Atlantic Monthly Roll V Folder 23
Ault, L. A. Roll III Book 2 Roll V Folder 19
Austin, O. P. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Austrian Embassy Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Ayme, L. H. Roll III Book 1
Ayres, Howard Roll III Book 1
Babbitt, E. H. Roll V Folder 22
Bacon, Robert Roll IV Book 5 Roll V Folder 21
Bain, George G. Roll III Book 1
Bainbridge, William E. Roll III Book 1
Baird, G. W. Roll III Book 2
Baird, William J. Roll III Book 2
Baldwin, Elbert F. Roll IV Book 3
Baldwin, Evelyn B. Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Baldwin, George E. Roll III Book 2
Baldwin, George M. Roll IV Book 3
Baldwin, James C. Roll IV Book 4
Ballard, Walter Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Bancroft, Frederick Roll V Folder 24, Folder 25
Banderetta Mines Roll V Folder 22, Folder 23
Bard, Thomas R. Roll IV Book 3
Barnes, Benjamin F. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4, Book 5
Barrels, David E. Roll V Folder 24
Barrett, John Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4, Book 5
Barring, H. Roll IV Book 3
Barrows, Dean Roll V Folder 23
Bass, W. L. Roll IV Book 4
Basso, Sebastian Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Bates, Arthur N. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Beale, G. P. Roll IV Book 4
Bean, Henry W. Roll IV Book 4 Roll V Folder 19
Beard, J. A. Roll III Book 1
Beardsley, Morris Roll IV Book 4
Beaton, George A. Roll III Book 2
Beaupie, A. M. Roll V Folder 19
Beck, William H. Roll V Folder 24
Beecher, John P. Roll IV Book 4
Beer, William C. Roll IV Book 3
Beneditt, James S. Roll IV Book 4
Benjamin, I. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Bennett, R. Roll IV Book 3
Bergholz, Leo Roll IV Book 4
Biddle, Nicholas Roll V Folder 19
Biglow, John Roll V Folder 19
Billow, Barrett and Company Roll IV Book 4
Bills, Charles B. Roll V Folder 23
Bliss, Ernest C. Roll III Book 2
Bliss, William H. Roll IV Book 4, Book 5
Blyth, Charles R. Roll V Folder 25
Blythe, Samuel G. Roll IV Book 4
Boardman, Mabel T. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4 Roll V Folder 24
Bohl, Henry Roll IV Book 3
Bolce, Harold Roll IV Book 4
Bonaparte, Charles J. Roll IV Book 3
Bond, W. W. Roll IV Book 4
Bonds, James Sr. Roll IV Book 4
Bonsal, Stephen Roll IV Book 4
Borah, William E. Roll V Folder 24
Bouchsein, Max Roll III Book 1
Bouie, Verne M. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Boulton, Henry L. Roll IV Book 4
Boutell, H. S. Roll IV Book 4
Bowen, Herbert W. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3 Roll V Folder 19, Folder 20
Boyd, W. W. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 4
Boye, Herbert C. Roll III Book 2
Boynton, Charles T. Roll V Folder 21, Folder 22
Bradley, William H. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 4
Bragg, Edward S. Roll IV Book 4
Braisted, William C. Roll IV Book 3
Brandeger, Frank B. Roll V Folder 21
Brandt, Eddy S. Roll IV Book 3
Braun, Marcus Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Breuer, John B. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3
Bridgman, H. L. Roll III Book 2
Brigham, Joseph H. Roll III Book 2
British Embassy Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Bristow, [?] Roll IV Book 4
Bromuell, J. H. Roll III Book 1
Bronson, W. Roll IV Book 3 Roll V Folder 19
Brooks, Benjamin H. Roll III Book 1
Bross, Ernest Roll IV Book 4
Brown, Clyde Roll V Folder 19
Brown, Philip Roll IV Book 3
Brown, Walter Roll IV Book 3 Roll V Folder 24
Brun, M. Constantine Roll IV Book 3
Bryan, J. H. Roll IV Book 4
Bryan, O. G. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Buchanan, William I. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5 Roll V Folder 21, Folder 22
Bukey, Jean M. Roll IV Book 4
Bullock, William E. Roll V Folder 24
Bunau-Varilla, Philippe Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4, Book 5 Roll V Folder 19, Folder 23, Folder 24
Bunker, William M. Roll V Folder 22
Burchell, N. W. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3
Burgeoise, Leon Roll V Folder 23
Burguin, A. P. Roll IV Book 3
Burke, M. J. Roll III Book 2 Roll V Folder 23
Burns, James Roll V Folder 21, Folder 23
Burrows, Julius C. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Burton, Theodore E. Roll IV Book 3 Roll V Folder 23, Folder 24
Busbey, L. White Roll IV Book 3, Book 4 Roll V Folder 23
Busch Haddenbausen, [?] Roll III Book 1, Book 2
Butler, Charles H. Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Butler, Nicholas M. Roll III Book 1 Roll V Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 25
Butler, Theodore E. Roll IV Book 4
Butterworth, E. M. Roll V Folder 24
Caldwell, John A. Roll IV Book 4
California Arabian Standard Company Roll V Folder 25
California Press Association Roll V Folder 24
Callahan, J. M. Roll III Book 2
Calvo, Joaquin Bernardo Roll III Book 1
Camp, Eugene M. Roll IV Book 4
Campagna, Matthew Roll IV Book 3
Campbell, James E. Roll III Book 2
Canadian Pacific Railroad Roll IV Book 4
Cannon, Joseph Roll V Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23
Capron, K. Roll V Folder 22
Carden, Lionel Roll V Folder 23
Carman, Heron L. Roll IV Book 3
Carmichael, Otto Roll IV Book 4
Carnegie, Andrew Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Carnegie Peace Endowment Roll V Folder 23, Folder 24
Carner, A. H. Roll IV Book 4
Carpenter, Frank Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Carr, William J. Roll V Folder 21, Folder 23, Folder 24 Folder 25
Carranza, Venustiano Roll V Folder 23
Carter, John R. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5 Roll V Folder 21
Cassell, William Roll V Folder 24
Cassini, Count Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Castro, Cipriano Roll V Book 19, Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 25
Ceballos, J. M. Roll III Folder 2
Cellere, V. Macchi di Roll III Book 2
C. E. Poole and Son Roll IV Book 3
Chadwick, F. E. Roll III Book 1
Chaffee, Adna R. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Chambers, D. A. Roll IV Book 3
Chambers, Julius Roll IV Book 4
Chamburn, Charles de Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Chandler, John Rice Roll IV Book 4
Chekib Bey Roll IV Book 4
Cherry, Albert Roll V Folder 19
Chilton, Robert S. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Chipman, G. Bowie Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Choate, Joseph H. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Choistoy, Henry L. Roll IV Book 4
Christian Herald Roll V Folder 22